(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Jason is 12 years old.
He wants to buy a video game.
It costs $60.
He does not have money.
He cannot get a job.
He is too young to get one.
He tried selling his old things.
He only made a dollar.
He tried doing homework for people.
He got caught.
He tried taking online surveys.
He ended up getting a computer virus.
He tried selling his handmade toys.
People thought they were ugly.
He tried dancing on the streets.
He only managed to get a few pennies.
He entered a drawing competition.
The prize was $100.
He lost.
He asked his parents if he could have
some money.
They said yes.
There was a catch.
He had to do chores.
He said yes.
His parents gave him $5 for every hour
he worked.